深影
ShinY
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影
ShinY
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.com
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影
ShinY
■
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.com
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影
ShinY
我叫琪拉·卡梅伦
My name is Kiera Cameron,
■
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.com
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影
ShinY
我从2077年来到这里
and I came here  from the year 2077.
我叫琪拉·卡梅伦
My name is Kiera Cameron,
■
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.com
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影
ShinY
我从2077年来到这里
and I came here  from the year 2077.
■
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.com
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影
ShinY
■
我从2077年来到这里
and I came here  from the year 2077.
深影
ShinY
■
我从2077年来到这里
and I came here  from the year 2077.
深影
ShinY
翻译： 闲鱼
变革从我们开始
Evolution is on our schedule.
■
我从2077年来到这里
and I came here  from the year 2077.
深影
ShinY
翻译： 闲鱼
变革从我们开始
Evolution is on our schedule.
翻译： 闲鱼
■
深影
ShinY
■
变革从我们开始
Evolution is on our schedule.
翻译： 闲鱼
战争从今天打响
The war begins now.
■
ShinY
变革从我们开始
Evolution is on our schedule.
翻译： 闲鱼
■
ShinY
翻译： 闲鱼
战争从今天打响
The war begins now.
翻译： 闲鱼
■
战争从今天打响
The war begins now.
艾米丽 没关系的
Emily, it's ok.
翻译： 闲鱼
■
战争从今天打响
The war begins now.
艾米丽 没关系的
Emily, it's ok.
翻译： 闲鱼
■
我也爱你
I love you, too.
翻译： 闲鱼
■
艾米丽
Emily!
翻译： 闲鱼
■
艾米丽
Emily!
■
校对：  闲鱼    后期： 小滔
艾米丽
Emily!
校对：  闲鱼    后期： 小滔
■
我必须接受这个现实
I have to accept the truth.
校对：  闲鱼    后期： 小滔
■
我也许永远也回不到他身边了
That I may never get back to him.
校对：  闲鱼    后期： 小滔
■
但是这并不意味着我就不去努力
That doesn't mean I have to stop trying.
■
我想要的只是这样
That's all I've ever wanted.
让一切回到最初 让我能会到家人身边
To put the pieces back together and return to my family.
对不起 琪拉
I'm sorry, Kiera.
艾力克 我能回家
Alec, I can go home!
我知道
I know.
但是我必须去救她
But I have to save her.
艾米丽 我穿越时间来就为了你
Emily, I travelled through time for you.
你
You.
我选的是你
I choose you.
这么说 我想我们做不成朋友了 是吧?
So I guess we're not gonna be pals then, huh?
我是没看出来
I don't see how.
有两个艾力克·赛德勒
There are two Alec Sadlers.
他让时间装置运转
He made the time device work.
他返回过去改变历史
He traveled back to change things
创造出另一条时间线
and created another timeline.
就是这一条
This one.
而它创造了终极未来
That's what created  the ultimate future
这个家伙就是从那来的
that this guy comes from.
时间旅行者先行 我们让一切重来
Travelers lead, let's knock all the dominos down.
如果情况紧急 你可以用这个
When things get too hairy, I want you to use this.
好了 让老大亲自给你送行
Alright, let's let the big man himself send you off.
长官
Sir.
你想躲过死亡 凯洛格?
You want to cheat death, Kellogg?
帮我 我教你怎么做
Help me, and I'll teach you how.
我只是机器上的一个螺丝 卡洛斯
I'm just a cog in the machine now, Carlos.
我不再有机会和那些大师交手
I don't get to play chess master anymore.
我怎么觉得不可信呢
Somehow I doubt that.
这是昨天的
That was yesterday.
她真是伤人心啊
She is a heartbreaker.
我们以企图谋杀艾力克·赛德勒的罪名逮捕你
You are under arrest for the attempted murder of Alec Sadler.
这条时间线对我们两个还是太小了
This timeline isn't big enough for the both of us.
我非常同意
I couldn't agree more.
我一直让另一个艾力克签署一系列的文件
I have been getting the other Alec to sign documents
让我取代他管理公司
that remove him and put me in the big chair.
这个会发射信号
This will send a signal.
如果没人听到 那么什么事也不会发生
If nobody hears it, nothing happens.
但是如果有人听到呢?
And if someone does hear it?
那么我们已经失败了
Then we've failed.
赛德勒先生撤销所有的起诉
Mr. Sadler is dropping all charges.
好的
Right.
交给你们了
All yours.
你成功了
You did it.
谢谢你 卡洛斯
Thank you so much, Carlos.
真的非常感谢
We really appreciate it.
好的
Good.
既然派朗已经回到正常人的手上
You can reciprocate by getting Piron to support my department's requests
作为回报 你可以让派朗支持我们警局某些要求
now that it's finally in the hands of a sane person.
哦好吧 又出什么事了?
Alright, what happened?
是凯洛格
Kellogg happened.
他设计让另一个我
He tricked other me
将公司的控制权转给他
into turning over control of the company to him.
我已经被踢出公司了
I've been kicked out.
我怎么一点都不惊讶呢?
Why am I not surprised?
我想知道未来是什么样子
I wonder what the future will hold.
有所期盼很好 不是吗?
Isn't it nice to wonder?
是的 确实很好
Yeah, it is.
我们现在怎么办?
What do we do now?
快跑!
Run!
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
你快走 我去尽力拖住他们
You keep going, I'll try to slow them down.
什么
What?!
他们是我的人 也许他们不会伤害我
They're my people, they're not gonna hurt me.
等我安全了 会去找你的
I'll contact you as soon as it's safe.
你最好来找我
You better.
哦 该死的!
Oh, shit!
喔 嘿 嘿!
Woah, hey, hey!
托金 别挡路
Tonkin, out of my way.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
韦弗 守在这里
Weaver take point.
罗林斯从侧边包抄 瓦斯凯作掩护
Rollins flank while Vasquez provides cover!
佐林 报告位置?
Zorin, status?
我在你们的六点钟方向
I've got our six.
追踪不到 信号消失
Track has gone,  I've lost the signal.
目标再次出现
Target is back.
还有十秒钟 警察马上到
10 seconds, I've got  inbound police.
尽快收网
Close the net.
哦 该死的
Oh, shit.
卡梅伦警官
Officer Cameron.
我这是在哪里?
Where am I?
你现在在CPS九号治疗湾
You're in CPS Med Bay Nine.
今天是几号?
What's the day?
九月二十五号
September 25th.
哪一年?
The year?
2080年
2080.
通知卡梅伦警员的家人她已经醒了
Have Officer Cameron's family notified she's awake.
家人?
Family?
你已经睡了三年
You've been asleep for three years.
欢迎回来 琪拉
Welcome back, Kiera.
超越时间线 终结季 第一集
我不记得被送进来
I don't remember being brought in.
我什么也不记得了
I don't remember anything.
你和其他几十个在行刑室爆炸中受伤的伤员
You were admitted with dozens who were injured
一起入院接受治疗
in the execution chamber explosion.
恐怖袭击?
The terrorist attack?
解放组织?
Liber8?
这都不重要了
It doesn't matter.
我们用药让你进入可控的昏迷状态
We initiated a controlled coma so that we could operate
以便我们进行手术 同时减轻你恢复时的不适
and spare you some of the recovery discomfort
但是不知为何我们无法将你唤醒
but for some reason we couldn't wake you up.
我们知道你醒来只是个时间问题
We knew it was just a matter of time before you came back to us.
你有什么想告诉我的吗?
Is there something you want to tell me?
我曾有过非常真实的经历 非常的真实
I had these vivid experiences, as real as anything.
不像是在做梦
More than a dream.
我
I...
我能记得所有的一切
I can remember all of it.
我明白
I understand.
这是完全可以理解的
It makes perfect sense.
你看 当CMR检测到你的大脑受到创伤时
You see, your CMR was designed to activate realistic simulation program
它就会启动实景模仿程序
when brain trauma has been detected.
妈妈?
Mom?
山姆?
Sam?
我想死你了
I missed you so much.
我也想你
I missed you, too.
你们有好多要聊的
You have some catching up to do.
我先出去了
I'll be right outside.
哦 看看你
Look at you.
看看你
我真不敢相信真的是你
I can't believe it's you.
我甚至不敢碰你
I'm scared to touch you.
我不敢相信你醒了
I can't believe you're back.
对不起我走了 我不想的 我从没想过
I'm so sorry I left, I didn't want to, I didn't mean to.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
我好想你
I missed you.
每天都想
I missed you every day.
我本应一直陪着你的
I should have been there for you and...
但是我却没有
and I wasn't.
没关系的
It's ok.
一切都很好
Everything is ok.
不好
It's not ok.
一点都不好 看看你
It's not ok. Look at you!
情感的压力让我们有点担心
This emotional stress is becoming a concern.
你在这干什么?
What are you doing here?
我来是让你平静下来
I'm here to calm you down.
琪拉 很高兴看到你醒过来
Kiera, I'm so pleased to see you back.
你任务完成的非常好
You've done an excellent job.
你已经改变了历史
You've changed the past.
拯救了未来
You saved the future.
妈妈?
Mom?
山姆?
Sam?
山姆
Sam!
琪拉?
Kiera?
琪拉 你还好吗?
Kiera, are you ok?
琪拉!
Kiera!
山姆!
Sam!
你还好吗?
Are you ok?
是艾力克
It's Alec.
山姆!
Sam!
是卡洛斯和我
It's Carlos and Alec.
起来
Come on.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
他刚才 他刚才还在这呢
He was just... he was just here.
你没有受伤 很安全 还活着
You're fine, you're safe, you're alive.
我没事 我没事
I'm ok, I'm ok.
琪拉 你现在出现了幻觉
Kiera, you are hallucinating.
遇到头部受创 我的CMR会启动实景模拟状态
My CMR goes into simulation mode in the event of head trauma.
慢点
Come on.
我没事 我没事
I'm ok, I'm ok.
交给我们了 谢谢
We've got it from here, thanks.
到底发生什么事了?
What the hell happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
发生什么事了?
What did happen?
我只知道巡逻的警官遇到一些重型武装的嫌犯
All I know is patrol came across some heavily armed perps.
他们已经悄悄溜走 现在不知所踪
They snuck their way out of the area and they escaped.
我们现在正在竭力追捕他们
We're trying to get a location on them
但是我们目前缺少相关的线索
but we're a little short on details.
好了
Ok.
带她离开这里 去一个安全点的地方
Get her out of here, take her some place safe.
好的
Sure thing.
我希望你明天尽早来我办公室
I want you in my office first thing tomorrow.
马塞勒斯?
Marcellus?
托金
Tonkin.
你见到我好像很惊讶
You look surprised to see me.
我没想到你会来执行这项任务
I didn't expect to see you pulling this duty.
你离开之后 情况更糟糕了
After you left, things got worse.
我们已经全员出动了
We moved everything up.
罗林斯 诺兰
Rollins, Nolan.
你认识的 瓦斯凯
You know Vasquez.
韦弗 还有佐林
Weaver, and Zorin.
你的目标呢?
What happened with your aim?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
你的任务是找到时间穿梭者并将其终结
Your mission was locate timers and neutralize them.
事情变得有点棘手
Things got complicated.
我看见你和她了 布拉德
I saw you with her, Brad.
卡梅伦
Cameron.
她现在是我们的目标
She's on the target list.
你怎么和她在一起?
What were you doing with her?
地方不错啊
Nice place.
这是谁的
Who's is it?
显然是我的
It's mine, apparently.
是的
Right.
另一个我 死了的那个
The other me, dead me,
紧紧握着金钱权力不松手的那个
grabbed the brass ring with both hands.
现金付款
Paid in cash.
艾力克?
Alec?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
好的
Ok.
我意识到一件事
I came to a realization.
什么事?
What's that?
我已经完成了我的任务
I accomplished my mission.
阻止解放组织
Stopped Liber8,
让他们不能按照他们的计划建造未来
prevented whatever future they might have built,
我还确保你绝不会创建那个破碎的未来
and I made sure you will never build the broken future
我来自的那个未来
that I came from.
这就是送我回来的原因 不是吗?
That was the reason for sending me back, wasn't it?
显然是的
Apparently.
是时候该为我自己着想了
It's time for me to focus on myself.
想想我想要什么
What I want.
你到底在说什么 琪拉?
What exactly are you talking about, Kiera?
憧憬
Longing.
渴望
Desire.
突然一下涌进我的脑海
It caught me a little by surprise.
我想回家 艾力克
I want to go home, Alec.
我需要你送我回去
And I need you to send me.
你们这些阴谋家在谋划什么呢?
What are you schemers scheming?
复仇
Revenge.
报复
Payback.
哦 她还不知道
Uh, she doesn't know.
我不知道什么?
What don't I know?
你把我留在派朗之后 凯洛格亮出他的底牌
After you left me at Piron, Kellogg played his ace card.
我被公司开除 他取而代之
I got the boot and he's taken control.
我想拿回我的公司
I'm trying to get my company back.
艾力克已经找到报复凯洛格的计划
Alec has a plan to make Kellogg pay.
让他损失惨重
And make it hurt.
让我担心的就是这损失惨重
It's the hurting part that concerns me.
怎么会呢?
How's that coming?
我们会控制几个街区
We've hit a few road blocks.
一切尽在我掌握
It's nothing I can't handle.
我们昨天晚上谈的都忘了?
What about our conversation last night?
这正是我在做的
That's exactly what I'm doing.
怎么讲?
How do you figure?
为了送你回到
In order to get you-
你该回到的地方
where you need to go,
我需要非常特别的技术
I need very specialized technology.
那个目前拥有
The one person who currently possesses
这项能送你回到你的未来的罕见技术的人就是
that very rare technology to get you back to your future is-
凯洛格
Kellogg.
凯洛格先生?
Mr. Kellogg?
柯蒂斯·陈来了
Curtis Chen is here for you.
谢谢了杰奎琳
Thank you, Jacqueline.
你做的不错啊
You're doing well.
这不能靠老天的眷顾
It's not by accident.
我能为你做什么 柯蒂斯?
What can I do for you, Curtis?
是我能为你做什么 凯洛格
It's what I can do for you, Kellogg.
是关于我的未来
Is this about my future?
一直都是
It always is.
好吧 听着
Ok, look.
在你用那些虚情假意的时间宗教谬论
Before you spellbind me with some hokey temporal
骗我之前
religious nonsense,
让我先把话说清楚吧
let me cut to the chase.
目前我真没看出来与你和你的朋友结盟
Right now I don't really see the advantage of aligning myself
对我有什么好处
with you and your friend.
我不是说最终一点可能都没有
I'm not saying it's not a possibility... eventually,
我只是需要先稳住自己在公司的位置 你知道的
I just need to get the lay of the land first, you know?
之后才能做出一些重大的决定
Before I make any important decisions.
你怎么会知道?
How will you know?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
他们是否重要 那些决定
If they're important, the decisions.
你看 所以你才需要我
See, that's where I come in.
我可以让你提前知道哪些决定非常重要
I can let you know in advance which decisions are key
能保护你的未来 哪些决定没有那么重要
to protecting your future and which decisions are not.
把这些时间旅行者看做一张地图
Think of the traveler as a road map.
一张通往冰冷未来的地图
A map to this grim future
而我是那个世界的军阀带领一支军队
where I'm some warlord leading an army.
不是未来
Not the future.
是现在
Right now.
你的步兵已经来到这条时间线了
Your foot soldiers are here in this time.
我可以帮助你利用他们
I can help you use them,
推进他们的行动
push their actions.
以合理的方式让时间线
Push the timeline in the right direction.
朝正确的方向发展
The right way.
我还是需要想想
I'm still gonna think about it.
当然这是你的特权
It's your prerogative, of course.
但是无论怎样
But one way or another,
你摆脱不了你的命运
your destiny will catch up with you
你会来找我
and bring you back to me.
来找我们
To us.
这样我就有所期待了
Then I have something to look forward to.
现在请原谅
Now if you'll excuse me,
我有些事情要处理一下
I've got some business to attend to.
当然
Of course.
有趣的一晚上
Interesting night.
哦 是的
Uh, yeah.
你可以这么说
You could say that.
除了全市停电和街头枪战
Between the power outage and street warfare,
我猜解放组织的活动会日益频繁
I'm guessing more Liber8 activity.
我担心可能是新的帮派
I'm worried it's a new faction.
有什么根据?
Based on what?
可靠线报
Solid intel.
琪拉·卡梅伦提供的线报?
Provided by Kiera Cameron?
监控视频显示她和解放组织成员一起
There's CCTV security footage of her with members of Liber8.
为他们效力
Working with them.
琪拉已经成功打入解放组织
Kiera's managed to infiltrate Liber8.
她一直在收集情报 能让我们
She's gathering intel that should lead to
顺藤摸瓜抓到组织的高级头目
some high-profile arrests.
多好的一个愿望啊
That's quite the promise.
不如说是可以实现的预言
More of a hopeful prediction.
我要结果
I want results.
不要预言
Not predictions.
收到
Copy that.
哦 你听说狄龙的事了吗?
Oh, did you hear about Dillon?
什么事?
What?
医生认为他已经康复了
Doctors cleared him.
随时可以出院
He'll be out any day.
我可以回去继续当警探了
I can go back to being a detective.
我不会这么早庆祝的
I wouldn't throw away that sport coat just yet.
有传言说他不想当警察了
Word on the street is he's done with the force.
我的个上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
我从来不知道你信耶稣
I never took you for a religious man.
你知道你刚才让我多难办吗?
Do you realize the position that you put me in?
我向你保证这是你最后一次
I promise this is the last time
为我打掩护
you'll ever have to cover for me.
你在说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
没什么
Nothing.
我只想竭尽所能保护你和警局
I just want to protect you and the department in any way that I can.
我已经带来了很多麻烦
I've caused enough damage.
各种各样的
Literally and figuratively.
你没事吧?
Are you ok?
没事
Yes.
好吧
Ok.
那为什么和我说说昨天晚上到底是怎么回事?
So why don't you tell me what happened last night?
布拉德想看看是否
Brad wanted to see if
我们已经成功阻止了凯洛格的黑暗未来
we had prevented Kellogg's dark future.
不幸的是 证据显示我们失败了
Unfortunately, proof that we failed showed up
六个重型武装的战士就是最好的证明
in the form of six heavily armoured soldiers.
那他们现在在哪里?
And where are they now?
我不知道
I don't know.
那布拉德呢?
And Brad?
从昨晚我就没有再见过他
I haven't seen him since last night.
我希望他也许能在里面策应我们
I'm hoping that he might be working them from inside.
也许能
Might be?
我很担心
I'm worried.
好吧 我们必须查出他们在哪里
Alright, we gotta figure out where these soldiers are
他们的计划是什么
and what they're planning.
盯住凯洛格
Target Kellogg.
他还有他那个变态脑袋瓜里的
They're connected to him and whatever he's cooking up
可怕计划与他们密不可分
in that twisted mind of his.
凯洛格 我的新主子?
Kellogg, as in my new overlord?
就是他
Same guy.
这可能不会像说起来这么容易
It's not gonna be as easy as it sounds.
凯洛格已经集聚了很多的权力和财力
Kellogg has consolidated a lot of power and money,
而他在警局的影响力
and his influence in this department
也不可小视
shouldn't be underestimated.
派朗的钱在这里依然很管用
Piron still holds the purse strings around here.
我想你一定能想出办法摆脱控制
I'm sure you can find a way around that.
哦 我毕竟是个警察 琪拉
Well, I'm still a cop, Kiera.
我还要遵规守法
I've got to follow the rules.
但是你却可以帮我拿到让我逮捕凯洛格的
But you could get me something concrete
真凭实据
that I can arrest Kellogg on
我们分工合作
and we could share the load.
搭档
Partner.
好吧
Ok.
我努力去搞定他
I will work on nailing his ass,
但是先去探探情况会很有意思
but it might be fun to shake the tree first.
你有什么计划了吗?
And what did you have in mind?
你是哪一个?
So which one are you?
好的那一个
The good one.
我想你们俩都会这么说的
I think you'd both say that.
我是唯一的那一个
I'm the only one.
那你有多好呢?
Then how good are you?
你知道多少?
How much do you know?
索尼娅告诉我了一点
Sonya told me a little bit.
把其他的事情串起来
Brought some other things together.
你的未来 还有我的
Your future, mine.
那些人是干嘛的?
Who are those guys?
政治活动方面的朋友
Political activist friends.
他们看起来很严肃
They look serious.
他们是很严肃
They are serious.
在进行社会变革方面
About making change.
比你的那些敌人聪明多了
Outsmart your enemy.
不让自己成为目标
Don't make yourself a target.
潜入其中 从内部瓦解
Embed, disrupt from the inside.
太巧了
This is serendipitous.
这也是我想过来和你谈的
That's what I came to talk to you about.
我洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
你手上还有进入派朗的员工卡吗?
Do you still have your employee access card to Piron.
他们还没有解雇我
They haven't fired me yet.
目前没有
Yet.
好极了
That's good.
也许你所说的变革
Maybe that change that you're talking about,
也许我们可以一起创造
maybe we can make it together.
玩低调?
Laying low?
保护者现在也许是我们的朋友
The protector might be our friend for the moment,
但是她依然为那个
but she still works for a system
要将我们除掉的体系效力 卢卡斯
that wants to bring us down, Lucas.
我们需要考虑生存下去然后消失
We have to start thinking about survival and disappearing.
有新情报了吗?
You have an update?
是的 但是你不会想听的
Yeah, but uh... you're not gonna like it.
看来我们在光环发布会上
It seems like all that effort we put into switching
调换艾力克·赛德勒的努力都付之东流了
Alec Sadlers at the Halo launch event was for nothing.
凯洛格抢先一步
Kellogg's pulled a fast one
并且将那小子赶出公司
and arranged to have the kid removed from his company.
现在王牌都在他手上
He's holding all the cards now.
凯洛格掌控派朗公司
Kellogg controlling Piron.
这对我们不是好消息
That can't be good for us.
我会告诉特拉维斯
I'll tell Travis.
还有
There's more.
有一个时间线事件和凯洛格的未来有关
There's some kind of temporal event connected to Kellogg's future.
保卫者对此怎么看?
What's the protector doing about it?
还不清楚
It's unclear.
为什么?
Why is that?
琪拉在保护布拉德
Kiera is protecting Brad.
他们是他的人
They're his people.
那我们不能相信她
Then we can't trust her.
你确定你都考虑周全了?
Are you sure you thought this through?
非常周全
Completely.
所以最后我和那个家伙说
So finally I say to the guy
如果我不能把直升飞机停在这
"if I can't land a helicopter on it,
那我买它干什么?
"what's the point of buying it?"
不好意思 女士 这是私人聚会
Excuse me, ma'am, this is a private party.
只有受邀的嘉宾才可以出席
Invited guests only.
真是屡试不爽啊
That never gets old.
哦 抱歉
Um, excuse me.
一会儿回来
This won't take a minute.
卡洛斯
Carlos!
真是意外啊
What a surprise,
我不记得你的名字在嘉宾名单上
I don't remember your name on the guest list.
但是你的名字一直都在
Yours, however, is always on the guest list.
真是荣幸之至啊
I'm flattered.
我来这是谈正事的 凯洛格
I'm here on business, Kellogg.
哦
Oh.
你们俩为什么不告诉我艾力克怎么了?
Why don't you tell us what happened with Alec.
你说的是哪一个呢?
Which one are you referring to?
别给我装了
Don't be a dick.
你在策划什么?
What are you up to?
正事
Business.
和卡洛斯一样
Just like Carlos.
你看 从我的角度看
Look, from where I was standing,
另一个艾力克是个麻烦
the other Alec was a problem.
说实话 他头脑发热
He was a shithead, to be frank.
你知道 我也知道
You knew it, I knew it.
我只是创造性的利用了这个局势
I just took care of the situation in my own creative way.
好吧
Fine.
那就把派朗还给不是麻烦的那个艾力克
Then give the Piron keys back to the Alec who isn't a problem.
我倒想了 但是董事会不知道我们知道的事情
I'd love to, but the board doesn't know what we know
让他们相信
and it might be a hard sell to them
时间旅行制造两个相同的人是很难的事情
with the whole time travel doubles thing, you know.
自相矛盾的说法
Paradoxically speaking.
为什么你不跟我们谈谈
Why don't you tell us about
来自布拉德未来的那些战士?
these soldiers from Brad's future?
对不起 是你的未来
I'm sorry, your future.
不好意思 再说一遍好吗?
Sorry, come again?
用英语最好?
In English, please?
超能装备 重型武器
Power suits, heavy weapons,
军阀凯洛格的未来生活?
warlord Kellogg future scenario?
布拉德都跟我们说了
Brad spelled it out for us.
也许你应该去和他谈谈
Maybe he's the one you should be talking to.
你的男朋友
Your boyfriend.
也许你的调查应该从那里开始
Perhaps you should start your investigation there.
我们走吧 琪拉
Let's go, Kiera.
哦 耶 !
Oh, yeah!
真是打脸啊 凯洛格
In your face, Kellogg.
立刻关闭
...Shut it down.
是来自域网外的攻击 我们整个网络已经被关闭
It's an outside DNS attack, our entire network shut down.
那就马上恢复
Well, get it back up.
一切都好吗 马修?
Everything alright, Matthew?
你知道不好 显然你是幕后策划
You know it's not, you're obviously behind it.
我们和现在的状况一点关系都没有
We have nothing to do with whatever is going on right now.
有人对你很不满吗 凯洛格?
Is somebody mad at you, Kellogg?
无论是谁在对这家公司进行网络攻击
Whoever just hacked into this company
他们都是在犯罪 卡洛斯
is breaking the law, Carlos.
为什么不去做好你的本职工作?
Why don't you do your job?
你知道吗?
You know what?
你说的对 对不起
You're right. I'm sorry.
我会彻查此事
I'll get to the bottom of this.
事实上 我认识一个很厉害的人
In fact, I know the perfect guy
可以帮助我们追踪
that can help us track down
这起十恶不赦事件的制造者
the perpetrators of this heinous act.
他在电脑方面非常厉害
And he's a whiz with computers.
刚才怎么回事?
What just happened?
完全不知道
I have no idea.
凯洛格一定在谋划什么 我有种感觉那些战士
Kellogg is up to something and I have a feeling those soldiers
只是冰山一角
are just the tip of the ice berg.
是啊 这是毫无疑问的
Yeah, no doubt about that.
听着 如果布拉德潜入他们当中
Look, if Brad is embedded with these guys
我不是在妄加评论
and I'm not judging,
我只是说 如果你有任何疑问
I'm just saying, if you have questions
也许你应该好好问问他
maybe you should press him for answers.
一定是凯洛格
It's gotta be Kellogg.
打开免提
Put him on speaker.
艾力克·赛德勒
Alec Sadler.
朱利安在那里吗?
Is Julian there?
他在 我们开的免提
He is, and you're on speaker phone.
朱利安 你被解雇了
You're fired, Julian.
你无法开除我 我早就辞职了
You can't fire me, I already quit.
随你了
However you like.
艾力克 我知道这次黑客攻击是你搞的
Alec, I know you're behind this hack.
弄好它
Fix it.
立刻马上
Right now.
否则我就和你势不两立
Or I take this to Defcon 1.
你偷走我的公司的时候我们就已经势不两立了
You already did that when you stole my company.
好吧
Ok.
你准备好了和我在大联盟里较量了吗 小子?
Are you ready to play big league hard ball with me, kid?
放马过来吧
Bring it.
CMR已经连线
And CMR is connected.
和以往一样
Just like old times.
你想念谷仓的时候吗?
You miss the barn?
每一天
Every day.
艾力克 我们开始工作前
Alec, before we get to work,
我需要知道你对凯洛格做了什么
I need to know what you did to Kellogg.
没有太过分
Nothing too harsh.
艾力克 你做了什么?
Alec, what did you do?
我只是把他锁在自己的系统之外
I sort of locked him out of his own system
然后下载并删除了所有的数据
and then downloaded and erased all the data
控制派朗公司设备的所有软件
and control software for Piron's equipment.
你是在自找麻烦
You're asking for trouble.
事实上 我只是在努力送你回家
Actually, I'm trying to send you home.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
所有派朗反物质时间旅行的研究
All of Piron's anti-matter time travel research
都在我偷的数据中
is in the data that I stole.
我想我们可以用这些时间想出办法
I thought we could use the time to figure out a way
利用他们公司的技术最终能送你回家
to exploit the company's tech and eventually send you home.
谢谢
Thank you.
真是让人激动啊
That's inspired.
凯洛格现在会忙于恢复数据
Kellogg's going to be so focused getting his business
他甚至没有时间弄清楚
back up and running he won't even have time to realize
我们的真正目的
what we're really up to.
好极了
Good.
你在忙这个的同时
While you're working on that,
我还希望你能帮助我找到布拉德还有那些战士
I'd also like you to help me find Brad and the soldiers.
我以为你不不管这事了
I thought you were staying out of it.
只是为了安心
It's just for my own peace of mind.
如果他和他们关系很好 我就不管了
If he's in tight with them, I'll back off.
但是如果他有麻烦了
But if he's in trouble...
我理解
I understand.
能帮我吗?
Can you do it?
也许
Maybe.
他们的装备也许依靠很先进的科技控制
Their gear is probably operating on some advanced tech.
奇数波长之类的
Odd wavelength stuff.
我可以对频谱进行一次扫描
I could do a sweep of the spectrum,
看是否某些地区出现了特别的能量标识
see if there's any areas with unique energy signatures.
这无法给你一个确切的地址
It won't give you an exact address,
但是我可以缩小到几个街区
but I can narrow it down to a few city blocks.
你可以穿上你的超级战衣到那里
You could go down there using your super suit
充当一个超级天线
as a kind of antenna.
我可以告诉你具体的建筑
I could give you a specific building.
好的 这已经够了
Alright, good enough.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
你们在分解超能装备
You're breaking down the power suits,
拆分核心组件
cannibalizing the core components.
是的
Something like that.
你们到底在做什么?
What exactly are you building?
这次任务是机密级别
This mission is a need-to-know basis,
你无权知道
and you don't need to know.
诺兰?
Nolan?
给他点时间
Give it time.
马塞勒斯有很多事要考虑 而你
Marcellus has a lot on his plate and you-
我怎么了?
What about me?
你不明白我们做的事
You can't see what we can.
好的 左转
Alright, take a left.
走到街区的尽头
Try the end of the block.
这需要花多长时间?
How long is this gonna take?
取决于你的速度
Depends on how fast you go.
我收回我说的话
I take it back.
我一点都不想念这个
I don't miss this.
你的CMR说你在说谎
Your CMR says you're lying.
好极了
Great.
该死的
Shit.
你在跟踪我吗?
Are you following me?
不是
No.
完全是巧合
It's a total coincidence.
你在干什么 琪拉?
What are you doing, Kiera?
男朋友出问题了?
Boyfriend issues?
算是吧
Something like that.
对我们所有人来说凯洛格的战士都是个问题
Kellogg's soldiers are a problem for all of us.
这件事不能听你一个人的
You don't get to call the shots.
提前通知我
Give me a head start.
我会让布拉德先离开 你们可以跟进
I'll clear Brad from the area, you can roll in,
支援我 做你们想做的
back me up and do your thing.
喔 信号增强了
Woah, the signal just spiked.
你正在接近
You're getting close.
艾力克说我们离他们很近
Alec says we're close.
你要帮我呢
Are you gonna help me out
还是我直接现在就停止整个行动呢?
or am I gonna shut this whole thing down right now?
查到了
Got it.
是你左手边的大厦 琪拉
It's the building to your left,  Kiera.
就是这里了
This is it.
嘿 提前通知我 记得吗?
Hey, head start, remember?
我改变主意了
I changed my mind.
听我说
Listen to me:
我看见他们作战
I have seen these men in action.
你需要抢占优势
You need to have the upper hand,
但是你目前没有
and right now you don't.
我可以答应你
I can play nice.
你有十分钟
You got ten minutes.
好极了
Perfect.
你真的会让加尔萨轻举妄动?
Are you seriously gonna let Garza try anything?
不会
No.
时刻准备给卡洛斯打电话
Get Carlos on speed dial.
要他随时准备好 无论在哪
I want him ready to roll, no matter what.
收到
Gotcha.
为什么要冒这个险?
Why take the chance?
事情没那么简单
It's not that simple.
我们一起服役
We served together.
多愁善感是不能打赢战争的 马塞洛斯
You don't win wars with sentimentality, Marcellus.
是不能
No, you don't.
打赢战争靠的是侦查是后备支援
You win them with recon and support.
托金安排我们的营地 我们的补给 我们的通讯
Tonkin arranged this place, our supplies, and our comm.
他都做到了
He's delivered
这是由我说的算
It's my call.
我们看事情如何发展
We'll see how it plays out.
这绝对不是来自现在的武器
That is definitely  not from now.
我正在录制这些 琪拉
I'm recording all this, Kiera.
你在你的时代看到过类似的东西吗?
You ever see anything like that in your time?
没有 对我是全新的
No, that's a new one.
好像是时间旅行六号分队
It's like time travel team six.
核心部件分解最多还需要十一天的时间
We have 11 days max before the core degrades.
如果我们还需要作战
If we're gonna have a fight
我们需要更多的医疗供给
we're gonna need more medical supplies.
队员们焦躁不安
Crew is on edge.
那是他们的问题 不是你的?
It's their problem, not yours?
马塞洛斯 这里一半的人我不认识
Marcellus, I don't know half of these guys.
你知道没有你我们这件事做不了
You know we can't do this  without you.
貌似他已经然他们相信他还是他们的人
Looks like he's convinced them he's one of them.
有人能从内部给我们输送情报好极了
It'll be nice having someone on the inside feeding us info.
哇喔 那是什么?
Woah, woah, what is that?
太酷了
It's cool.
能拿起来给我看看吗 看起来好像是一支钢笔?
Can you grab me that, it looks like a pen?
小心她 琪拉
Watch her, Kiera.
她在做什么?
What's she doing?
让她撤出来
Get her out of there.
快让她撤出来
琪拉 布拉德很安全
Kiera, Brad is safe.
你得马上离开
You need to leave.
交给我了!
Got her!
枪法不错啊
Nice shot.
咬我啊
Bite me.
注意我们身后 他们也许还会有人过来
Watch our backs, there could be more of them.
艾力克 帮我离开这里
Alec, get me out of here.
马上!
Now!
艾力克 艾力克 我被发现了
Alec, Alec, I'm burned.
快帮我找条出路 快点!
I need a way out, now!
好的 等一下 等一下 给我点时间!
Ok, hang on, hang on, just give me a second!
现在你出局了
Now you're out.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我也知道
That makes two of us.
你来这做什么?
What are you doing here?
我也想问你这个问题
I can ask you the same thing.
你现在无权问任何问题
You're not in a position to be asking any questions.
我是警察
I'm a police officer,
那个人是是我正在调查的
and that man is a suspect
一个案子的嫌犯
in an investigation that I'm conducting.
现在 我不知道你以为你们在做什么
Now, I don't know what you think you're doing here
但是我知道你们和马修·凯洛格有关
but I do know that you're involved with Matthew Kellogg,
警察也这么认为
and so do the police.
我给卡洛斯打电话
I'm calling Carlos.
不要
Don't!
不要是什么意思?
What do you mean, "don't"?
不要相信他
Don't trust him.
你也许把凯洛格当盟友
You might consider Kellogg an ally
但是他只对一件事感兴趣
but he's only interested in one thing.
凯洛格
Kellogg.
这是在浪费时间
This is a waste of our time.
把她扔下去
Toss her.
马塞洛斯 她也许会有用
Marcellus, she could be useful.
有用?
Useful?
他跟你说什么了?
What'd he tell you?
什么都没说
Nothing.
他想杀我 但是没成功
He tried to kill me, and he failed.
显然是的
Apparently not.
我们去追她!
Let's go after them!
不用了!
Stand down!
我们打包离开这里
We pack up and we move.
同意
Agreed.
很快这里会挤满警察
This place will be crawling with cops in no time.
真险啊
That was close.
太危险了!
Too close!
你看见艾米丽了吗?
Have you seen Emily?
有一会儿没看见了
Not for a while.
下车
Get out!
马上
Now!
好的 随时通知我
Alright, keep me posted.
好的
Yeah.
Alright.
反恐特勤组搜查了整栋楼
So SWAT cleared the building,
没有发现我们的新朋友
there's no sign of our new friends.
真是意外啊
Surprise, surprise.
怎么了?
What is it?
感觉又回到了从前
I just feel like we've been down this road before.
解放组织的重演
It's Liber8 all over again.
嗯 这次我们知道他们为凯洛格效力
Well, this time we know they're working for Kellogg
他们内部还有我们的人
and we've got a man on the inside.
如果情况是这样
If that's the case,
为什么我们还谁也没抓到呢?
why don't we have anybody in custody yet?
也许布拉德会联系我们
Maybe Brad will reach out.
我们不能靠也许抓人啊
We can't count on "maybe".
你知道 自从你被打晕了之后 你有点
You know, ever since you got knocked out there's been,
我不知道 有点不一样
I don't know, something different.
对不起
Sorry.
我有点心不在焉
I've been preoccupied.
2077年的一些回忆
Thoughts of 2077.
家
Home.
山姆
Sam.
当然
Of course.
我需要相信我依然有机会回到那里
I need to believe that path still exists for me.
我还能再见到他
That I'll be able to see him again.
我支持你回家
Well, I support you going home.
我不喜欢 但是我支持你
I'm not happy about it, but I support you.
希望你能回家
To going home.
敬回家
你晚了
You're late.
我必须要小心
I had to be careful.
你说是关于凯洛格和他的新朋友
You said this was about Kellogg and his new friends.
我来这也只是因为这个
That's the only reason I'm here.
所以有话快说
So make it quick.
我觉得我们不能再任由凯洛格
I don't think any of us can afford to let Kellogg
不断强大了
become more powerful.
更加独裁 建立自己的军队
More insulated, build and control an army
创造他自己的历史
that shapes history his way.
你想说什么?
What are you saying?
我想说有利于你和解放组织的事情
I'm saying what's good for you and Liber8
很有可能对凯洛格不利
is most likely what's bad for Kellogg.
你想让我们除掉凯洛格?
You want us to take out Kellogg?
帮你干脏活儿?
To do your dirty work?
不是
No.
不 我想你有很好理由干掉凯洛格
No, I think you've got plenty of good reasons to kill Kellogg.
我只是觉得时间不等人
I just don't think you can afford to waste any more time.
再见 贾思敏
Goodnight, Jasmine.
这个邮包是给你的
This package was delivered for you.
保安已经查过了
I've cleared it with security.
谢谢你 杰奎琳
Thank you, Jacqueline.
用你的左手把它放在地上
好啊 伙计
Hiya, pal.
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.com
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.com
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub